http://www.thefsb.com/policies-disclosures/

×
Effective November 18, 2020, all FSB branch lobbies will be open by appointment only. Visit our COVID-19 Update page to learn more.
Personal / Basic Business
Username:
Password:
Login
Enroll now.
|
Forgot Password?
Username:
Password:
Login
Lost
or Damaged Token
Forgot
password or PIN?
Advanced Business
Username:
Password:
Login
First Time User
|
Forgot Password?
Unlawful Internet Gambling Act
Your privacy concerns are important to us and protecting your personal information is our first priority.
Facts:  What does First State Bank do with your personal information?
Why - Financial companies choose how they share your personal information.  Federal law gives consumers the right to limit some but not all sharing.  Federal law also requires us to tell you how we collect, share, and protect your personal information.  Please read this notice carefully to understand what we do.
What - The types of personal information we collect and share depend on the product or service you have with us.  This information can include:
Social Security number and account balances
Account transactions and transaction history
Credit history and credit scores
How - All financial companies need to share customers' personal information to run their everyday business.  In the section below, we list the reasons financial companies can share their customers' personal information; the reasons First State Bank chooses to share; and whether you can limit this sharing.
To limit our sharing:
Call 866-372-1275 or
Visit us online: Privacy Opt Out
Please Note:
If you are a new customer, we can begin sharing your information 30 days from the date we sent this notice.
When you are no longer our customer, we continue to share your information as described in this notice.
However, you can contact us at any time to limit our sharing.
Questions?
Call 866-372-1275 or Contact Us
Who we are
Who is providing this notice?
First State Bank, a Michigan banking corporation, and its affiliate, First State Investment Services LLC.
What we do
How does First State Bank protect my personal information?
To protect your personal information from unauthorized access and use, we use security measures that comply with federal law.  These measures include computer safeguards and secured files and buildings.
How does First State Bank collect my personal information?
We collect your personal information, for example, when you
open an account or deposit or withdrawal money
pay your bills or apply for a loan
use your credit or debit card
We also collect your personal information from others, such as credit bureaus, affiliates, or other companies.
Why can't I limit all sharing?
Federal law gives you the right to limit only
sharing for affiliates everyday business purposes - information about your creditworthiness
affiliates from using your information to market to you
sharing for nonaffiliates to market to you
State law and individual companies may give you additional rights to limit sharing.
What happens when I limit sharing for an account I hold jointly with someone else?
Your choices will apply to everyone on your account.
Definitions
Affiliates
Companies related by common ownership or control.  They can be financial and non-financial companies.
First State Investment Services LLC
Nonaffiliates
Companies not related by common ownership or control.  They can be financial and non-financial companies.
Third party credit card companies, investment companies and insurance companies
Joint Marketing
A formal agreement between non-affiliated financial companies that together market financial products or services to you.
Third party credit card companies, investment companies and insurance companies
Reasons we can share your personal information
Does First State Bank Share?
Can you limit this sharing?
For our everyday business purposes - such as to process your transactions, maintain your account(s), respond to court orders and legal investigations, or report to credit bureaus
Yes
No
For our marketing purposes - to offer our products and services to you
For our affiliates' everyday business purposes - information about your transactions and experiences
Yes
No
For our affiliates' everyday business purposes - information about your creditworthiness
